<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">FoodRecipe</string>

    <string-array name="Recipes">
        <item>Burger</item>
        <item>Tortilla</item>
        <item>Burrito</item>
        <item>Spaghetti Bolognese</item>
        <item>Pizza</item>
        <item>Pasta With Shrimps</item>
        <item>Pasta With Chicken</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="Time">
        <item>Time : 30 min\n\n

        Ingredients:\n
            1 small onion, diced\n
            500g good-quality beef mince\n
            1 egg\n
            1 tbsp vegetable oil\n
            4 burger buns\n\n

            Step 1:\n
            Tip 500g beef mince into a bowl with 1 small diced onion and 1 egg, then mix.\n\n
            Step 2:\n
            Divide the mixture into four. Lightly wet your hands.
            Carefully roll the mixture into balls, each about the size of a tennis ball.\n\n
            Step 3:\n
            Set in the palm of your hand and gently squeeze down to flatten into patties about 3cm thick.
            Make sure all the burgers are the same thickness so that they will cook evenly.\n\n
            Step 4:\n
            Put on a plate, cover with cling film and leave in the fridge to firm up for at least 30 mins.\n\n
            Step 5:\n
            Heat the barbecue to medium hot (there will be white ash over the red hot coals – about 40 mins after lighting).
            Lightly brush one side of each burger with vegetable oil.\n\n
            Step 6:\n
            Place the burgers, oil-side down, on the barbecue. Cook for 5 mins until the meat is lightly charred.
            Don’t move them around or they may stick.\n\n
            Step 7:\n
            Oil the other side, then turn over using tongs.
            Don’t press down on the meat, as that will squeeze out the juices.\n\n
            Step 8:\n
            Cook for 5 mins more for medium. If you like your burgers pink in the middle, cook 1 min less each side.
            For well done, cook 1 min more.\n\n
            Step 9:\n
            Take the burgers off the barbecue. Leave to rest on a plate so that all the juices can settle inside.\n\n
            Step 10:\n
            Slice four burger buns in half. Place, cut-side down, on the barbecue rack and toast for 1 min until they are lightly charred.
            Place a burger inside each bun, then top with your choice of accompaniment.\n\n
            Thats all!\n</item>
        <item>Time : 35 min\n\n
        Ingredients:\n
            8 oz. boneless, skinless chicken breast halves, cut into 1/2-inch pieces\n
            2 tsp. fajita seasoning\n
            3 Tbsp. light cream cheese or chive cream cheese, softened\n
            2 (10-inch) flour tortillas\n
            1/2 cup packed shredded lettuce\n
            1/4 cup (1 oz.) Sargento® Shredded Sharp Cheddar Cheese - Fine Cut\n
            1/4 cup salsa\n\n
            Step 1:\n
            Heat medium skillet over medium-high heat; coat with non-stick cooking spray.\n
            Add chicken; sprinkle fajita seasoning over chicken.\n
            Cook, stirring frequently, 4 minutes or until chicken is cooked through.\n
            Set aside to cool.\n\n
            Step 2:\n
            Spread cream cheese over tortillas; top with lettuce, chicken and cheese.\n
            Fold two outside edges over filling; roll up burrito-style.\n
            Cut diagonally in half. Serve with salsa.\n\n
            Enjoy it!\n</item>
        <item>Time : 40 min\n\n
        Ingredients:\n
            6 Flour Tortillas\n
            Refried Beans\n
            Mild Thick N Chunky Tomato Salsa\n
            250g cooked rice\n
            500g leftover chicken, shredded\n
            250g grated cheese\n
            1 ripe avocado\n\n
            Step 1:\n
            Pierce the soft flour tortillas package and warm it in the microwave for 35-45 seconds.\n\n
            Step 2:\n
            Using the back of a spoon, spread a thin layer of the refried beans over each tortilla, almost to the edge. The refried beans help to hold the ingredients and tortillas together.\n\n
            Step 3:\n
            Add cooked rice, again spreading with the back of a spoon, leaving a gap of about 3cm from the edge of the tortilla.\n\n
            Step 4:\n
            On top of the rice, add sliced avocado forming a rectangular shaped “column”. Fresh ingredients like lettuce, red cabbage, or tomato work great, too. \n\n
            Step 5:\n
            Use a fork to shred the leftover chicken into bite-sized chunks and layer on top of the column of avocado.\n\n
            Step 6:\n
            Alternatively, to prepare uncooked chicken, place oil in large frying pan over a medium heat, add the chicken and cook until the outside is golden and the meat thoroughly cooked.\n\n
            Step 7:\n
            Spoon a dollop of salsa on top of the chicken.\n\n
            Step 8:\n
            Sprinkle grated chicken on top of the salsa.\n\n
            Step 9:\n
            Roll your burrito\n\n
            Thats all!\n</item>
        <item>Time : 40 min\n\n
        Ingredients:\n
            2 tbsp olive oil\n
            400g/14oz beef mince\n
            1 onion, diced\n
            2 garlic cloves, chopped\n
            100g/3½oz carrot, grated\n
            2 x 400g tin chopped tomatoes\n
            400ml/14fl oz stock (made from stock cube. Ideally beef, but any will do)\n
            400g/14oz dried spaghetti\n
            salt and pepper\n\n
            Step 1:\n
            Heat a large saucepan over a medium heat. Add a tablespoon of olive oil and once hot add the beef mince and a pinch of salt and pepper.
            Cook the mince until well browned over a medium-high heat (be careful not to burn the mince.
            It just needs to be a dark brown colour). Once browned, transfer the mince to a bowl and set aside.\n\n
            Step 2:\n
            Add another tablespoon of oil to the saucepan you browned the mince in and turn the heat to medium.
            Add the onions and a pinch of salt and fry gently for 5-6 minutes, or until softened and translucent. Add the garlic and cook for another 2 minutes.
            Add the grated carrot then pour the mince and any juices in the bowl back into the saucepan.\n\n
            Step 3:\n
            Add the tomatoes to the pan and stir well to mix. Pour in the stock, bring to a simmer and then reduce the temperature to simmer gently for 45 minutes,
            or until the sauce is thick and rich. Taste and adjust the seasoning as necessary.\n\n
            Step 4:\n
            When ready to cook the spaghetti, heat a large saucepan of water and add a pinch of salt.
            Cook according to the packet instructions.
            Once the spaghetti is cooked through, drain and add to the pan with the bolognese sauce.
            Mix well and serve.\n\n
            Ready to eat!\n</item>
        <item>Time : 40 min\n\n
        Ingredients:\n\n
            For the base\n\n
            300g strong bread flour\n
            1 tsp instant yeast (from a sachet or a tub)\n
            1 tsp salt\n
            1 tbsp olive oil, plus extra for drizzling\n\n
            For the tomato sauce\n\n
            100ml passata\n
            handful fresh basil or 1 tsp dried\n
            1 garlic clove, crushed\n\n
            For the topping\n\n
            125g ball mozzarella, sliced\n
            handful grated or shaved parmesan (or vegetarian alternative)\n
            handful of cherry tomatoes, halved\n\n
            Step 1:\n
            Make the base: Put the flour into a large bowl, then stir in the yeast and salt.
            Make a well, pour in 200ml warm water and the olive oil and bring together with a wooden spoon until you have a soft,
            fairly wet dough. Turn onto a lightly floured surface and knead for 5 mins until smooth. Cover with a tea towel and set aside.
            You can leave the dough to rise if you like, but it’s not essential for a thin crust.\n\n
            Step 2:\n
            Make the sauce: Mix the passata, basil and crushed garlic together, then season to taste.
            Leave to stand at room temperature while you get on with shaping the base.\n\n
            Step 3:\n
            Roll out the dough: if you’ve let the dough rise, give it a quick knead, then split into two balls.
            On a floured surface, roll out the dough into large rounds, about 25cm across, using a rolling pin.
            The dough needs to be very thin as it will rise in the oven. Lift the rounds onto two floured baking sheets.\n\n
            Step 4:\n
            Top and bake: heat the oven to 240C/220C fan/gas 8.
            Put another baking sheet or an upturned baking tray in the oven on the top shelf.
            Smooth sauce over bases with the back of a spoon. Scatter with cheese and tomatoes, drizzle with olive oil and season.
            Put one pizza, still on its baking sheet, on top of the preheated sheet or tray.
            Bake for 8-10 mins until crisp. Serve with a little more olive oil, and basil leaves if using. Repeat step for remaining pizza.\n\n
            Delicious!\n</item>
        <item>Time : 30 min\n\n
        Ingredients:\n
            8 ounces fettuccine\n
            1 pound medium shrimp, peeled and deveined\n
            Kosher salt and freshly ground black pepper, to taste\n
            8 tablespoons (1 stick) unsalted butter, divided\n
            4 cloves garlic, minced\n
            1/2 teaspoon dried oregano\n
            1/2 teaspoon crushed red pepper flakes\n
            2 cups baby arugula\n
            1/4 cup freshly grated Parmesan\n
            2 tablespoons chopped fresh parsley leaves\n\n
            Step 1:\n
            In a large pot of boiling salted water,
            cook pasta according to package instructions; drain well.\n\n
            Step 2:\n
            Season shrimp with salt and pepper, to taste; set aside.\n\n
            Step 3:\n
            Melt 2 tablespoons butter in a large skillet over medium high heat.
            Add garlic, oregano and red pepper flakes, and cook, stirring frequently,
            until fragrant, about 1-2 minutes.\n\n
            Step 4:\n
            Add shrimp and cook, stirring occasionally, until pink, about 2-3 minutes; set aside.\n\n
            Step 5:\n
            Melt remaining 6 tablespoons butter in the skillet. Stir in pasta, arugula and Parmesan
            until arugula begins to wilt, about 2 minutes. Stir in shrimp.\n\n
            Step 6:\n
            Serve immediately, garnished with parsley, if desired.\n\n
            Thats all!\n</item>
        <item>Time : 35 min\n\n
        Ingredients:\n
            2-3 boneless skinless chicken breasts, diced into bite sized pieces\n
            1 tsp Italian seasoning\n
            1/2 tsp garlic powder\n
            1 medium yellow onion, minced\n
            3 cloves garlic, minced\n
            16 oz dried short-cut pasta\n
            24 oz jar of your favorite marinara sauce\n
            water to fill empty marinara sauce jar\n
            1 cup mozzarella cheese\n
            1/2 cup parmesan cheese\n
            salt and pepper, to taste\n
            additional dried Italian seasoning, optional\n
            fresh parsley and/or basil, minced for garnish\n\n
            Step 1:\n
            To a large pot or skillet (I used my dutch oven),
            add a drizzle of olive oil and heat over MED-HIGH heat.
            Add chicken, season with salt, pepper,
            Italian seasoning and garlic powder.
            Cook about 5 minutes, until chicken is most of the way cooked through.
            Remove to a plate.\n\n
            Step 2:\n
            Add onion and garlic to the pot and cook about 2-3 minutes, until soft.
            Pour in marinara sauce, fill up empty sauce jar with water and add to the pot.
            Bring to a boil, then reduce to a strong simmer.\n\n
            Step 3:\n
            Add chicken and pasta, stir, then cover and cook for 10-15 minutes, until pasta is cooked to your liking.
            Stir in parmesan cheese and 1/4 cup of the mozzarella cheese.\n\n
            Step 4:\n
            Sprinkle remaining 3/4 cup mozzarella cheese on top of the dish and cook another 2-3 minutes,
            until cheese is melted and gooey.\n\n
            Step 5:\n
            Sprinkle with additional Italian seasoning if desired, and garnish with parsley or basil.\n\n
            Tasty\n</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>